spiritair.com 2010-12-31

# Spirit Airlines - cheap tickets, cheap flights, discount airfare, cheap hotels, cheap car rentals, cheap travel

##  Spirit Airlines Online Privacy Policy

At Spirit Airlines, when you visit spirit.com we hold your privacy concerns in the highest regard. This policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use it, and when we share it with third parties. Our policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. 

If our information practices change in the future, we will let you know by posting the revised policy on spirit.com. 

###  What kind of information do we collect?

We collect information -- such as your name, e-mail address, billing address, phone number, and credit card number -- that you provide to us when you book a reservation or participate in a contest, promotion, or survey. We also maintain a record of your online booking history. This information can be used to help us improve our site design and your online experience.

###  How do we use your information?

When you book a reservation at spirit.com, we use the information you provide us to process your reservation. We will also send you an e-mail message informing you that your reservation has been confirmed. Additionally, we may need to contact you via e-mail or phone if we have other questions or information regarding your reservation. 

When you opt-in to receive our Red Light Specials and spirit.com special offers, we use the e-mail address you provide to send you weekly notices. We do not rent or sell your information to any third party.

###  Do we share your information with third parties?

We contract with third parties to assist us in maintaining and managing our customer information, to fulfill promotions, and to communicate with our customers. However, we do not authorize any of those third parties to use your information in any other way. When we offer contests and promotions, or join with another company to do so, customers who choose to participate in those contests and promotions may be asked to provide personal information in order to participate. That information may then be used by us and the other partners to notify winners or to fulfill promotional obligations. 

We do not rent, sell, or share any personally identifiable information we collect to or with any unaffiliated third party without your consent.

###  How do you remove your information from the spirit.com e-mail list?

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer to stop receiving information from us about our Red Light Specials and spirit.com special offers via e-mail, please visit our Sign-Up page accessible from the home page. You may also opt-out of receiving communications from us by sending us an e-mail message at [customer@spirit.com](mailto:customer@spirit.com). Please include your e-mail address and full name with your request. 

Please note that when you book an online reservation, we will contact you via e-mail to confirm your reservation. In addition, we may need to contact you via e-mail or phone if we have other questions or information regarding your reservation.

###  How and why do we use cookies on spirit.com?

A cookie is a small data file that Web sites often store on your computer's hard drive when you visit. Spirit Airlines uses cookies, but we do not store personally identifiable information in your cookie. The information stored in your cookie is only accessible by the Spirit Airlines Web servers. Other Internet users and companies cannot access this information.

We use cookies in order to improve your online experience. Cookies enable us to keep track of your reservation as you book on our site. They also allow us to recognize customers who have saved their info with us when they visit, and to provide those customers with their account information. If you save your info with Spirit Airlines or book on our site, we use cookies to monitor and maintain information about how you use our site and what you book. If you have not saved your info with us or booked from our site, we may monitor and maintain information about your use of our Web site in a manner that does not identify you. In either case, this information helps us to serve you better by improving our site design, as well as our products, services, contests, and promotions. 

Through our use of cookies, we track and maintain the identity of the Web site you visited immediately prior to visiting Spirit Airlines. Keeping track of the site you came from prior to visiting spirit.com can help us to improve our site design. We do not otherwise track any information about your use of other Web sites. 

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your Web browser. However, if you turn off cookies, we will not be able to track your reservation, which means you will be unable to book on our site. Nor will we be able to recognize you as a customer who has saved your information with us, so you will be unable to access (or change or delete) your account information. 

###  How do we make sure your reservation is secure?

Protecting your reservation information is our priority. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to ensure the security of your online information. To check the security of your connection, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser window after you access our secure server. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending upon your browser), then SSL is active. To double-check for security, look at the URL line of your browser. If you have accessed a secure server, the first characters of our site's address should change from "http" to "https." 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect from you online.

###  What about links to other Web sites and services?

Spirit.com may contain links to other sites that are not under our control. These Web sites have their own policies regarding privacy, and you should review those policies before visiting these sites. Spirit Airlines has no responsibility for linked Web sites and provides these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors. 

###  What if you have questions, comments or concerns?

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our privacy policy please contact us via e-mail at [customer@spirit.com](mailto:customer@spirit.com).

Thank you for reading our privacy policy.

Last Updated February 1, 2005
